[
	{
		"question": "Simon Say's, Say 456",
		"answers": ["456"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Simon Says, Whats 10+6+7+3",
		"answers": ["26", "twenty-six", "twenty six", "twentysix"]
	},
  {
    "question": "Don't Respond",
    "answers": ["no"]
  },
  {
		"question": "Simon Says, Say f",
		"answers": ["f"]
	},
  {
		"question": "Whats 4 x 2",
		"answers": ["no"]
	},
  {
		"question": "Simon Says, Tell My How Many Letter's Of The Alphabet There Are",
		"answers": ["26", "twenty-six", "twenty six", "twentysix"]
	},
  {
		"question": "Say yes",
		"answers": ["no"]
	},
  {
		"question": "Simon Is Asking, Whats 1+6",
		"answers": ["7", "seven"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Look At A Meme",
		"answers": ["no"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Simon Say's Look At A Loop",
		"answers": ["..loop"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Simon Say's, say qwert",
		"answers": ["qwert"]
	},
	{
		"question": "STOP",
		"answers": ["no"]
	}
]
